exclusive confirmed okay do we do okay
exclusiva confirmada vale do we do vale
we'll see let's see what's left to know well what's
ya veremos a ver falta por saber pues
left to know well name confirmed
falta por saber bueno nombre confirmado
color confirmed streaming platform
color confirmado plataforma de streaming
and at the time that we leaked the
y en el momento que hemos filtrado la
information here at the salsería
información aquí en la salsería
okay what they've done this afternoon was
vale lo que han hecho est tarde han sido
publish the website okay but they've
publicar la página web vale pero han
published the website but they haven't
publicado la página web pero no han
made any announcements on social media they haven't
hecho ningún anci en redes no han hecho
made any announcements on social media I mean we
no han hecho ningún anuncio en redes o
found it this afternoon by
sea lo hemos encontrado esta tarde de
chance I don't know what we were looking for
casualidad no sé qué estábamos buscando
But anyway something else let's see This is in 20
Pero bueno otra cosa a ver Esto es en 20
minutes But anyway the
minutos Pero bueno se han hecho eco los
media has also echoed
medios también
this news Auron Play and Villin
de de esta noticia auron Play y villin
would have broken up according to the
habrían roto según el creador de
content creator Javi Oliveira okay they have
contenido Javi oliveira vale se han
echoed it in several media outlets
hecho eco en varios medios de
and I think it's great because
comunicación y me parece Genial porque
also [ __ ] the truth is that it's
además [__] la verdad es que se
quite appreciated when credits are given
agradece bastante cuando se dan créditos
okay it's an exclusive Look I'm going to
vale es una es una exclusiva Mira os voy
tell you something true because there are a
a decir una cosa de verdad porque hay
lot of people trying to discredit This
mucha gente intentando desacreditar Esto
okay what I have said is what I have
vale lo que yo he dicho es lo que yo he
said okay there are many times when
dicho vale hay muchas ocasiones en las
I have given an exclusive and then
que yo eh he dado una exclusiva y luego
people come up to me and say Oh but
me viene la gente y me dice Ay pero es
you said  that this was with h and
que tú dijiste que esto era con h y
then it's written without h I mean no don't
luego se escribe sin h o sea no no me
come to me with nonsense okay don't tell me don't
vengáis con tonterías vale no me digáis
come to me with more nonsense okay I mean
no me vengáis con más tonterías vale o
everyone knows eh the appreciation that
sea todo el mundo sabe eh el aprecio que
I have for eh well for these two
yo tengo por Eh bueno por estos dos
content creators as well as for many
creadores de contenido al igual que por
others no but [ __ ] they are people who have
otros muchos no pero [__] son gente que
always treated me very well
a mí siempre me han tratado muy bien
obviously These are news that I have to
evidentemente Son noticias que yo tengo
give I know that they understand
que dar sé que ellos lo entienden
perfectly it may sit better or
perfectamente le pueden sentar mejor o
worse with them that I have to give this type of
peor que yo tenga que dar este tipo de
news but if I have the exclusive eh
noticias pero si tengo la exclusiva eh
if I have the exclusive tied up I'm going to give it
si tengo la exclusiva atada la voy a dar
okay And obviously I think you have to
vale Y evidentemente yo creo que hay que
be stupid okay eh but I'm not saying it for
ser lelo vale eh pero no lo digo por
any creator because I think no
ningún creador porque creo que ningún
creator has questioned me or anything like that
creador me ha puesto en duda ni nada por
okay But yes yes people of
el estilo vale Pero si sí gente de
Twitter Twitter accounts no let's see You have to
Twitter cuentas de Twitter no a ver Hay
be stupid to think that I'm
que ser lelo para para pensar que yo me
going to get burned by news like that I'm not
voy a quemar con una noticia así no me
going to get burned by something like that If I
voy a quemar con una cosa así Si te
'm telling you that it's confirmed it's that it's
estoy diciendo que está confirmado es
confirmed I mean don't give it another
que está confirmado O sea no le deis más
thought I know that there are many accounts on
vueltas yo sé que hay muchas cuentas en
Twitter that are superfans of the couple eh
Twitter que son superfan de la pareja eh
as a couple okay And they want to hold on to
como pareja vale Y quieren aferrarse a
something that is not reality okay
una cosa que no es la realidad vale que
yes auron said that he has a
sí que auron ha dicho que tiene una
sweatshirt that very well That's perfect that
sudadera que muy bien Que perfecto que
I'm telling you that they are not together I
yo te estoy diciendo que no están juntos
'm telling you I don't follow their day to
yo te estoy diciendo Yo no sigo el día a
day okay I don't follow the day to day
día de ellos vale No sigo el día a día
of what they have been saying in the Stream
de lo que han ido diciendo en el Stream
but apparently Well yes they have been
pero por lo visto Pues sí han ido
pretending let's see they have a friendship and I
fingiendo a ver tienen una amistad y
think that they will have affection for each other for
creo que cariño se van a tener toda la
life obviously unless
vida evidentemente a no ser que pase
something bad happens which I think will not be the
algo feo que creo que no va a ser el
case and hopefully it's not worth it because I think they are
caso y ojalá que no vale pues yo creo
going to mention each other fondly
que se van a mencionar con cariño
for life okay I don't know if they are
durante toda la vida vale Yo no sé e si
going to if they are going to speak out I
se van a si se van a pronunciar ellos
think it's not worth it from what I
creo que no vale por lo que tengo
understand No man, let's see there will come a
entendido No hombre a ver llegará un
time in the next few weeks when
momento en las próximas semanas en las
maybe there will not be a
que a lo mejor no van a ha ser un
live together like the other time but there
directo juntos como la otra vez pero
will come a time in some
llegará un momento en algún en algún
live or something that they will say Hey look, it
directo o algo que dirán Oye pues mira
's true that we are not okay or I mean they
que es verdad que no estamos vale o sea
will surely say it Not for nothing
lo van a decir seguramente No por nada
but because they are not going to be deceiving
sino porque no van a estar engañando a
people infinitely you know yeah  it's
la gente de forma infinita sabes sí que
true that they don't have to give
es verdad que no tienen por qué dar
explanations about their private lives but no, they do
explicaciones de su vida privada pero no
n't live together anymore for real. I mean, I know there
no viven juntos ya de verdad O sea sé
are a lot of Twitter accounts and
que hay muchas cuentas de Twitter e
Felix, a kiss, I know there are a lot of
Félix un beso sé que hay muchas cuentas
Twitter accounts that are stubborn in clinging to
de Twitter emperradas en aferrarse a una
something that isn't real, okay, I mean, I
cosa que no es real vale o sea os lo
'm telling you, I'm not going to get burned by
estoy diciendo no me voy a quemar con
this information, for God's sake, we're not
esta información por Dios no estamos
talking about if this platform
hablando de si la plataforma esta
had been blue. Imagine if I
hubiera sido azul Imagínate que me
had made a mistake with the color and the
hubiese equivocado en el color y el
name, okay, well, okay, but I was more or less on
nombre vale bueno Vale pero más o menos
track. But it's that in this, no, it's not that I'm not on
encaminado iba Pero es que en esto no no
track or I'm not on
es que no vaya encaminado o no vaya
track. It's that I'm confirming
encaminado Es que te estoy confirmando
the news for you, soul, a kiss, okay. I'm
la noticia alma un beso vale Te estoy
confirming the news, okay, I confirmed it
confirmando la noticia vale la confirmé
in the morning and I confirmed it
por la mañana y la re que te confirmé
in the afternoon, no more turns, there's no more turns, it's not
por la tarde sin más no hay más vueltas
that Auron mentioned a sweatshirt, it's not that
no es que auron ha mencionado sudadera
Auron mentioned a
no es que auron ha mencionado un
documentary, it's that, no, I don't care
documental es que que no que me da igual
that they said like they had
que ellos dijeron como que tenían
leaks and a billion Setup was changed
goteras y se cambiaba billin de de Setup
but it hasn't changed, let's see, the
pero no se ha cambiado a ver se ha
Setup has changed but it has changed,
cambiado de Setup pero se ha cambiado de
but quite changed, okay, Dom Javi
Setup pero bien cambiado vale dom Javi
Te  I swear this is the first time I don't see
Te juro que es la primera vez que no veo
to become a member it must be El Whisky
para hacerme miembro debe ser El Whisky
or that I'm playing cyberpunk while I
o que estoy jugando a cyberpunk mientras
write to you LoL a kiss it's the first time I do
te escribo LoL un beso es la primera vez
n't see to become a member eh It's
que no veo para serme miembro eh Está al
next to the subscribe button okay eh I
lado del botón de suscribirse vale eh lo
said it okay so I mean I'm not going to
he dicho vale o sea es que no voy a
enter into debates okay I'm not going to
entrar en en debates vale no voy a
enter into debates of yes yes yes no what if
entrar en debates de si sí de si no de
now I don't know what what if now
que si ahora no sé qué de que si ahora
a Twitter account comes up saying
me sale una cuenta de Twitter diciendo
let's see nobody eh I know that I know that there are
vamos a ver nadie eh sé que sé que hay
people who are trying to discredit me
gente que está intentando desacreditarme
But simply because it's me okay It's not
Pero simplemente porque soy yo vale No
that this information was on
es que esta información estaba en
Twitter no this information was not on
Twitter no esta información no estaba en
Twitter on Twitter there were rumors and
Twitter en Twitter había rumores y
suspicions Why Well because they had
sospechas Por qué Pues porque habían
noticed that there was something strange here eh
notado que aquí había una rareza eh
Because they had noticed that here I don't know what
Porque habían notado que aquí no sé qué
okay very well but one thing is
vale muy bien pero una cosa son las
suspicions and another thing is what I am
sospechas y otra cosa es lo que yo te
here to tell you exclusively the day before
vengo a contar en exclusiva antes de
yesterday what I am here to tell you
ayer lo que yo te vengo a contar en
exclusively okay No Francisco no Javi you
exclusiva vale No Francisco no Javi tú
made a video without informing yourself
hiciste un vídeo sin informarte
Francisco Take a walk around the park I'm
Francisco Date una vuelta por el parque
going to repeat it again confirmed  absolutely
te lo voy a volver a repetir confirmado
confirmed okay no it was already
confirmadísimo vale no es que ya estaba
on Twitter not long ago on Twitter there were
en Twitter de hace no en Twitter estaban
rumors people saying no this no
los rumores la gente diciendo no esto no
this and multi-accounts also making
esto y multicuentas también inventándose
things up no what I'm here to tell you is
cosas no lo que yo te vengo a decir es
confirmed absolutely confirmed they broke up at
confirmado confirmadísimo han roto en
some point well they're going to confirm it
algún momento pues lo van a confirmar
without further ado I'm not going to get into a debate
sin más es que no voy a entrar a debatir
Fuentes Miami Miami to me man no
Fuentes Miami Miami me lo hombre no
Fuentes Miami confirmed it to me No if you
Fuentes Miami me lo confirmó No si
want I'll put here the conversations
quieres te pongo aquí las conversaciones
that I've had with the people that I've had
que he tenido yo con la gente que haya
really it's that
tenido que tener de verdad es que
you guys believe how do you believe
ustedes os creéis que cómo os creéis que
things work that I have to
funcionan las cosas que yo tengo que
reveal the sources that I have to tell you
revelar las fuentes que yo os tengo que
how it's not worth it I was going to see it here
comentar como no vale iba a verlo aquí
but I think Karime is sending it to me
pero creo que me lo está mandando Karime
Ah no yeah well let's see auron's brother
Ah no si bueno a ver el hermano de auron
posted an Instagram story
ha puesto una historia de Instagram
they have to be together I understand anyway
tienen por qué estar juntos entiendo en
all pretty diffuse we'll see how it
fin todos bastante difusos veremos Cómo
evolves for example directly
evoluciona por ejemplo directamente
confirmed the news that they are no longer
confirmó la noticia la de que ya no
together I mean attitude that woke up
están juntos digo actitud que despertó a
the sleeping beast brother dauron Play
la bestia dormida el hermano dauron Play
this little message dedicated to him I've been investigating for 52 hours I'll
este mensajito le dedicó llevo 52 horas
give you an exclusive
de investigación os doy una exclusiva
Give me
Denme
days without sleeping  studying everything when
días sin dormir estudiando todo cuando
in truth the Source is a
en verdad la Fuente es un mensaje de
3 second WhatsApp message I am a
WhatsApp de 3 segundos soy Agente
Secret Agent of the FBI well he doesn't deny it
Secreto del FBI bueno no lo desmiente
okay No the Messi vergan didn't give an
vale No el Messi vergan no dio una
exclusive the Messi verga commented The
exclusiva el Messi [__] comentó La
donation that they made to Sara
donación que le hicieron a Sara de
really really is that it
verdad de verdad es que me
irritates me you don't understand between rumors and
irritável no entendéis entre rumores y
confirm the difference you don't know
confirmar la diferencia no la conocéis
rumors and confirm okay rumors and
rumores y confirmar vale rumores y
confirm Auro's brother doesn't deny it he doesn't
confirmar el hermano de Auro no lo niega
deny it he's telling me that Eh
no lo desmiente me está diciendo que Eh
well that I have said that I have
bueno que que yo he dicho que lo he
confirmed I don't know what I don't know how much and in
confirmado no sé qué no sé cuánto y en
reality I only confirmed it with a
realidad solamente lo confirmé con un
couple of WhatsApp well they were exactly
par de WhatsApp bueno fueron exactamente
a call in the morning another at
una llamada por la mañana otra al
noon and a few audios in the
mediodía y unos cuantos de audios por la
afternoon those were the three chats with
tarde eso fueron las tres charlas con
three people that I had to get to
tres personas que tuve para llegar hasta
where I wanted without further ado okay without further ado what
donde yo quería sin más vale sin más lo
Messi verga comments is a donation
que Comenta Messi [__] es una donación
that yes that yes that
que eso sí que
yes that we talk about okay
e eso sí que de eso sí que hablamos vale
or so what Messi verga comments The
o sea lo que Comenta Messi [__] La
donation that they make to him there okay well
donación que le hacen aí vale bueno
Messi vergan and everyone okay on Twitter
Messi [__] y todos vale en Twitter
mm it is a multi-account okay Because yes it
mm es una multicuenta vale Porque sí que
is true that there are people who
es verdad que hay gente que
m yes it is true that  There are people who
m sí que es verdad que hay gente que
are speculating just as they have been
está especulando al igual que han estado
speculating about this breakup that I already
especulando con esta ruptura que ya os
confirm to you okay the breakup is
la confirmo vale la ruptura está
confirmed and Well, you're going to see it
confirmada e Pues es que lo Vais a ver
in the next few days,
en las próxim en los próximos días
surely okay But as for them to be
seguramente vale Pero ya el que estén
speculating about Billin that he
especulando con billin que estuviera que
was having something with Ribor or that
estuviera teniendo algo con ribor o que
Auron was having something with Paulet,
auron estuviera teniendo algo con paulet
I told you here in the video, I
yo aquí os dije en el vídeo yo aquí os
told you here in the video that they deny it to me
dije en el vídeo que a mí me lo
okay, they deny it to me, they
desmienten vale a mí me lo desmienten a
tell me that this is nonsense okay I
mí me dicen que estos son tonterías vale
put my hand in the fire for a fact
pongo la mano en el fuego por hecho
because they deny it, I can't
porque me lo desmienten no la puedo
put it in the fire, obviously good
poner en el fuego evidentemente buenas
Javi can you send my aunt
Javi puedes mandarle un saludo a mi tía
Rosamel Forrito a greeting Greetings from Chile, let's
rosamel forrito Saludos desde chile a
see if you want, I'll kiss it for you Andy Let's see, I
ver si quieres te lo roso Andy A ver no
can't Let's see, I can't put my hand in the
puedo A ver no puedo poner la mano en el
fire for this information okay
fuego por por estas informaciones vale
because of the fact that they deny it to me
por el hecho de que a mí me lo
okay because of the fact that they deny it to me,
desmientan vale por el hecho de que a mí
this rumor that Auron
me desmientan este rumor de que auron
has something with me, they
tenga nada con
deny it to me  absolutely worth what I
a mí me lo desmienten rotundamente vale
believe what I believe There is
lo que yo creo lo que yo creo Es que no
nothing as they have denied it to me and
hay nada por como me lo han desmentido y
for some data worth what I believe There is
por algunos datos vale lo que yo creo Es
nothing now evidently
que no hay nada ahora evidentemente
and evidently because I can't put my
e evidentemente por no puedo poner la
hand in the fire Hey okay what they
mano en el fuego Oye vale a mí lo que me
tell me is that no, in fact he is still
dicen es que no que de hecho sigue
friends with both of them, the millor
teniendo amistad con los dos el millor
wants to have something with villin for a
quiere tener algo con villin desde hace
long time It's not a joke what
tiempo No es broma a mí lo que me
pissed me off was not this tweet okay This
mosqueado no fue este tweet vale Este
tweet was posted after I
tweet lo lo puso después de que yo
broke the exclusive because it seems the wasp nest was
sacara la la exclusiva porque se se se
a bit stirred no and and they
movió un poco la avispero no y y le
were giving him more fuel No, I
estaban dando como más más leña No yo
'm single stop screwing me and getting me
estoy soltera dejen de joderme y meterme
into gossip especially the multi-accounts
en chisme especialmente las multicuentas
that have nothing more to do than
que no tienen nada más que hacer que
invent things there are issues that
inventar cosas hay asuntos que deben
people should resolve for themselves and I
resolver las personas por sí mismas y
'm sick of being involved in things that
estoy harta de que me metan en cosas que
I have no reason to talk about or
yo no tengo por qué hablar o que
relating anything of mine with that
relacionen cualquier cosa mía con eso
find a life these are my networks and not
búsquense una vida son mis redes y no
everything I post has to do with a
todo lo que pongo tiene que ver con un
topic What are you referring to? You are referring to this
tema A qué se refiere se refiere a este
tweet that you deleted  I mean, just when I
tweet que borró o sea justo cuando yo
uploaded the video Paulet tweeted this let's see
subí el vídeo paulet tuiteó esto a ver
if it's true [ __ ] it really pisses me off it really
sí que es verdad [__] que me mosquea
pisses me off I'm
que te cagas me mosquea que te cagas
not going to deny this tweet but I'm going
este tweet no os lo voy a negar pero voy
to trust my source because what's
a confiar en mi fuente porque es que qué
going on Ah okay
pasa Ah vale
mm I trust my source and I don't think so
mm Confío en mi fuente y creo que no
but this isn't the account it's not the same
pero esta no es la cuenta no es la misma
Ah okay the screenshot wasn't verified a
Ah vale es que no estaba verificada la
kiss this is weird this t It's so
captura un beso yo es rarete este t Es
weird this t has mocked me
que rarete es que este t me ha moqueado
hyper I tweeted this paulete through the nauter
hyper eso lo teteo paulete por la nauter
flay no I don't know Karime I don't think
flay no no lo sé Karime no creo que
anyone has noticed nter flay
nadie haya hechado cuenta nter flay
except the usual four bad guys from
menos los cuatro malillos de siempre de
Twitter and I'm telling you okay I mean I take
Twitter e ya os digo vale o sea me hago
responsibility for my words not for what
responsable de mis palabras no de lo que
you guys understand okay It's not that I
ustedes entendáis okay No es que en
was on Twitter for weeks on
Twitter ya estaba desde hace semanas en
Twitter I wasn't on Twitter there were
Twitter no estaba en Twitter estaban los
rumors of people noticing
rumores de la gente dándose cuenta de
this detail and Of this other detail I
este detalle y De este otro detalle yo
'm giving you confirmation no but it
te estoy dando la confirmación no pero
's that today he said that a sweatshirt that
es que hoy ha dicho que una sudadera que
okay that very good but I'm
vale que muy bien pero que te estoy
telling you that they broke okay And  They
diciendo que han roto vale Y a mí Esto
flatly deny this to me, it's ok to me, They
me lo desmienten rotundamente vale a mí
flatly deny this to me and they
Esto me lo desmienten rotundamente y Me
tell me that it's not worth it, this is
comentan que no que no vale esto es
as far as I can
hasta donde os puedo
read [Music]
leer